{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application."
    },
    {
      "name": "asdf",
      "description": "asdf",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "asdf",
      "description": "asdf",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "name": "New Deck",
      "description": "New\n",
      "id": 8
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "How do you modify the state of a different React component? asdfasdfa",
      "back": "Not at all! State is visible to the component only.",
      "deckId": 2
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "Is react router fun?",
      "back": "No, not at all. It is pure evil.",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdfasdfasdfasdfasdf\n",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasd",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasd",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "asd",
      "deckId": 6,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 6,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdfasdf",
      "deckId": 6,
      "id": 21
    }
  ]
}